It's nice.
Is it okay?
Excuse me?
I meant your drink!
You're crying!
BLOODHOUNDS 2
Last month,
Min-beom had a physical at our clinic,
so we have a baseline for comparison.
His liver enzymes
are over 30 times that baseline.
-Thirty times?
-Yes.
He is in critical condition.
This can't be caused by alcohol.
I'd like to tentatively suggest
that there might be drugs in his system.
What kind of drug?
We'll know
once all the test results are back.
The best way to confirm
is to secure a sample of his drink.
When do you expect him to recover?
At this point, it's unclear if he will.
In the worst case,
he may need a liver transplant.
WILL WEE EVR MEET?
HOW ARE THE BOYS?
DU-YEONG, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE WE LAST TALKED
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO THE BOYS?
THEY'RE OKAY FOR NOW
LET ME KNOW RIGHT AWAY
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS
-Mr. Min.
-Hello.
How is President Hong?
It's not looking good.
Oh dear.
I will pray for his recovery.
Thank you very much. Yes.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Do you know her?
I've never seen her before.
Whoa, hey.
Are you sure about that?
I swear I've never seen her.
Excuse me.
When she kissed me,
a thin plastic film slid into my mouth.
Then I suddenly got dizzy,
my legs gave out,
and I collapsed onto the floor.
And right here,
she squeezed some kind of liquid
into my mouth.
And she asked me questions.
What questions?
I can't remember.
You kind of started talking
without even realizing it, right?
Yes, something like that.
Oh my.
Why? What is it?
It's called a truth serum.
If you take it,
it lowers your inhibitions
and makes you talk about
everything on your mind.
I heard it's used for dates and stuff.
Like narcotics?
Probably.
Is it like a drug
used to force a confession?
I would think so.
She's a smart one.
Did you know
Min-beom was coming here today?
Yes, the booking was made last week.
By whom?
His secretary.
Go to the hospital for a blood draw.
Then call me later.
Do you have my number?
-Yes, you gave it to me last time.
-Okay.
Shall we all have a talk?
Only Secretary Cho and the bartender
knew Min-beom was coming here today.
But I don't think the bartender did it.
For now,
Gun-woo and I'll go see the secretary.
Gwang-mu, could you track down that woman?
She might be operating
where young people hang out.
That might be more up your alley.
Okay.
-Be careful. She's got the hands of a pro.
-Mr. Min, I'm a pro too.
-Gang-yong.
-Yes?
Can I go with Mr. Moon instead?
Why?
If Woo-jin goes with Mr. Moon,
he might use his hand.
Is that okay, Gwang-mu?
Yes, that would be better.
-Then let's move.
-Okay.
-Let's go, Gun-woo.
Excuse me, Mr. Min.
I think this is President Hong's coat.
Are you ready, Gun-woo?
I am.
That's so nice to hear.
-Mr. Moon.
-Yeah?
I'll protect you.
That's so reassuring.
Is this the perk
of running with the champion?
Well, off we go too.
NO CALLER ID
Answer it, but don't say anything first.
Is the chaebol okay?
You…
What did you put in his drink?
You still don't get it,
you fucking bastard.
Fight me, or you're fucked.
I'll chop off your coach's hand,
rip out your mother's tongue,
and force her into a brothel overseas.
Damn it.
As for the chaebol's cousin,
I'll melt his face off with acid.
Make an enemy of me,
and every money-hungry fucker
becomes your enemy too.
How do you think I killed
that cop you saw stabbed to death?
A rat from the same precinct
sold him out for 50 million won.
Gun-woo.
Money buys everything.
I'll give you the money I promised.
Just give me one fight.
Damn it.
KIM GUN-WOO
Fine, fuck it.
In three days, your coach loses his hand.
Your mom will be next.
Just wait.
I'm familiar with these pricks.
They bleed people dry,
and even sell their organs,
those beastly bastards.
Gun-woo. To take down a beast,
you should become fearless.
Show an inch of weakness,
and these bastards will pounce.
You hear me?
What should I do?
To take down a beast…
you must be more beastly than the beast.
I told you
to turn your heart into cast iron.
When your heart is iron,
your fist becomes a blade.
Then you stab him.
With pricks like these,
you have to finish them off. Otherwise…
your family pays the price.
Hello.
Yes.
Won-yeong.
Min-beom got hurt.
Let's get inside.
Do you have a reservation?
-We're here to see the owner.
-Just a moment.
Party of two coming in.
-Go ahead.
-Thanks.
-I'm not going.
-Go home already, girls.
It's a heart. That's insane!
Gwang-mu!
-Gwang-mu!
-Hi.
What brings you all the way here?
Look at that necklace.
-Is it your mom's?
-Pretty, huh?
-Good grief.
-So what's up?
I'm looking for someone.
Who? Is he gay?
It's a woman.
Why come here, then?
Hey, hands to yourself. Have fun, okay?
You know everyone in this area.
How about lowering my interest a bit?
You little devil.
-Please.
-It's up to you.
You know I'm good.
Who is she? Let me see.
Hey, let's go to the back room.
-Follow me.
-Okay.
-Hey, Gun-woo.
-Yes?
-You can't be out here alone.
-Okay.
When I got here,
I told you Min-beom got hurt.
But you didn't even ask how he was doing.
Why did you sell him out
to those bastards?
You went to college on a scholarship
from the Iil Group Foundation.
That was Min-beom's decision.
He hired you as his secretary, okay?
What didn't he do for you? Tell me!
You bastard.
Did you need more money or what?
Hey.
Right now, that poor bastard is…
He can't even open his eyes.
How could you
stab him in the back like that?
Cho Won-yeong!
Is this how low you'll go?
-Don't yell at him.
-Hye-seon.
-Go inside.
-Stop it!
Go inside. Now!
It wasn't your fault!
Look.
Those bastards cut me like this.
Go inside, Hye-seon.
Won-yeong.
Tell me what happened.
You have to tell me
so I can keep you safe.
I'll take care of it.
It's okay.
Have a seat and tell me, please.
Well?
It's too grainy to tell,
and she's so basic.
Come on, take a closer look.
With this?
How do you expect me to do that?
You should lower
that interest rate for me.
At least tell me something
before you haggle.
You tell me something.
There is nothing to work with here.
You know that drug?
The stuff that makes you spill your guts…
It's Truth Game.
That's what it's called?
Yes, Truth Game.
That girl slipped something to the waiter.
I think it was that drug.
You'll have to lower
that interest for me now.
You remembered something, didn't you?
-There is this guy.
-Yeah.
He smuggles it into the country.
Where is that punk now?
-Lower that interest by 5%?
-Forget it, you little thief.
-Just this once, please!
-Stop it.
-Help me.
-Let go.
-Please, just this once.
-Damn it.
-Just this once.
-Fine, 5% it is!
-Hey, call him now.
-Yes, sir.
Give me one minute.
He's just a friend.
I see.
-I'm serious.
-Okay.
I was coming home after buying some beer
at the convenience store.
A hand forced its way in
as I closed the door.
Yes.
Those bastards kicked me
in the stomach.
Then they tied me to a chair.
If I screamed,
they said they'd melt my face with acid.
Now…
-Do you remember their faces?
-Sir.
I think I can take it from here.
Can she be excused?
Thank you.
Go inside.
What did they do to her hand?
They rubbed some kind of ointment on it
before slicing it open.
Maybe a numbing agent. She felt no pain.
What did they look like?
There were three of them.
The big guy had
large eyes with a deep eyelid crease.
And he was strong.
The one who did all the talking
had thick eyebrows
and knew exactly
how to get inside my head.
And?
The man who cut my sister's hand
was gaunt, with a receding hairline
and an odd look in his eyes.
He looked like a junkie.
Did those three seem tight?
They barely talked to each other.
But they worked like a well-oiled machine.
Anything else?
They asked if you were
President Hong's relative.
Those bastards did their research.
And…
It's okay. Go on.
I also told them
where Gun-woo and Woo-jin were staying.
-Should I call them now?
-No.
If they make a move first,
it will compromise Won-yeong.
We need to protect him.
For more reasons than one.
I'll tell Mr. Joo
to put more boots on the ground.
It's even better.
We can nab them if they show up.
The guys in Security Team 3 are all elite.
They said that if I talked,
they'd kill my whole family--
Won-yeong.
Don't worry.
I'll assign more undercover cops
to your sister and this house.
Tell her to act normally
for her own safety.
I'm really sorry.
If they'd done that to my kids,
I would've done the same.
It's not your fault.
Our family is our weak spot.
President Hong…
Is he all right?
Now you ask?
I'm sorry.
LEE WOO-JEONG
CLASS 39
Just pray, will you?
Hello, Woo-jeong.
He has arrived.
What's wrong with him?
You are Kim Gun-woo.
I am.
-See?
-I'm a huge fan!
Don't you remember me?
You dropped Hong Jong-min
with a left body shot
and signed this for me.
TO JANG JUN
THANK YOU, KIM GUN-WOO
That's right. I remember!
Yes, that was me!
Right, hello.
Nice to meet you again.
It's such an honor.
Thank you. Is this for real?
I'm so happy for you.
By the way, what can I do for you?
Kim Gun-woo
is desperately looking for this lady.
Have you seen her?
That's Gi-na.
Yeah, I know her.
We sort of had a romantic thing going on…
Did you sell her the Truth Game?
I sure did.
Where do you think she is?
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Have a good night.
Mr. Min, this is Moon Gwang-mu.
What's the situation?
I tracked her down. Her name is Gi-na.
I'm going to the gambling den
where she works.
Really? That's wonderful.
You put your faith in me.
I can't let you down, can I?
Maybe you could help me out
with my investigation later.
I'd be honored.
You know, my dream was to become
a homicide detective.
Let's meet up and talk it through,
and then we'll move out together.
Sounds good. Where should I wait?
Can you head over
to Gun-woo and Woo-jin's hotel?
One of my guys found a lead
based on that photo you gave me.
Really?
Okay, I'll see you there.
Yes, see you soon.
Come on in.
Everyone, I'd like you
to meet Lee Woo-jeong.
He's our team's newest investigator.
Hello, nice to meet you.
At my alma mater,
there is the Green Pine Tree Club.
It means to remain evergreen like a pine,
upholding justice and equality
in our society.
It was started by our seniors.
It's a secret society
for the top of the class.
I met him there.
Meet Tae-yeong. She used to be
with the Cyber Investigation Division.
Nice to meet you.
It's an honor to meet a CID legend.
I'm not a boxer,
but I'm a huge fan of the sport.
I've been following you
since the Rookies during the pandemic.
Thank you.
Moon Gwang-mu here. It's an honor.
The honor is mine.
This is the first time
I'm meeting a top student.
Hey, you've met me.
The second, then.
Seriously.
What was your name again?
I'm Hong Woo-jin.
I was in that same Rookies Tournament
you watched.
I'm sorry, I…
So, Woo-jeong.
Does the "Woo" in your name
mean "to help"?
It actually means "to excel."
Mine means "to help."
I hope we get to know each other
and help each other.
Sure. Next time we meet,
I'll say hello first.
Does your name "woo" also mean "to help"?
-Mine means "friend."
-I see.
Should we also start
a society like the Green Pine Tree Club?
Three different Woos unite
and move forward.
How about Three Woo Club?
I love that idea.
Long live the Three Woo Club, okay?
But Woo-jin, can we get to work?
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
OCTO ROMA NATURALIA CASE FILE
I'll start the brief on the case report.
The watch in the photo you sent us
is a limited edition.
Only two people in Korea
bought this watch.
A professional soccer player in Europe,
and the other is
a man named Yun Tae-geom.
That's the bastard.
Is that him?
Yes, we fought him.
Yun Tae-geom, born in 1990.
In March 2009, he enlisted as
a Class 179 NCO, Special Warfare Command.
He served in the 17th SF Brigade,
specializing in explosives.
His squadmate says
he was a brainiac with nimble hands
who was a natural at cooking up IEDs.
In April 2020,
he was dishonorably discharged.
It's classified
and yet to be confirmed. I…
checked his Family Relations Certificate.
SPOUSE: HAN EUN-JI, DECEASED
CHILD: YUN MIN-A
He has a young daughter.
Where is she?
She's in Daejeon with her grandmother.
I'm still probing the wife's case.
Where is Yun Tae-geom now?
On paper, he went to Thailand last year
and hasn't returned since.
I think he reentered the country
on a forged passport.
Okay, can we gather here for a second?
-Yes.
-Okay.
This is the head.
And this is
Yun Tae-geom.
He's Special Forces,
the fixer, and the muscle.
This is Kang In-beom.
It's unclear what role
this next bastard plays.
But Secretary Cho says he is…
A yap?
Yes, that's the vibe.
Let's first go over what we know.
This is the junkie doctor.
Perhaps this bastard cooked up
the drug used on Min-beom.
Thick eyebrows here is likely the broker,
hiring thugs, strategizing,
and gathering intel.
He probably orchestrated Kang's jailbreak.
He preps whatever they need.
Sir, there's a sixth one.
The computer whiz.
They've got a crowd.
That payroll must be huge.
Gang-yong.
I was waiting to tell you in person.
In front of Golden Slumber earlier,
I got a call.
-On your cell?
-Yes.
What did he say?
It was a threat. Fight in their league,
or they would hurt everyone around him.
The phone number was
probably restricted.
Did he say anything else?
Gun-woo.
About the detective
who died in front of us,
someone from his own station
sold him out for 50 million won.
Let's keep our circle small.
Just between us, okay?
Yes.
In a sense,
they're more intelligent and specialized
than Kim Myeong-gil's crew.
But there's no need to chicken out.
Justice is on our side.
We have a few tasks,
but they need to happen all at once.
Gwang-mu and Gun-woo,
please go see that woman.
-Okay.
Woo-jeong, trace the bastard
who stabbed Detective Choi. Pull the CCTV.
Will do.
Woo-jin, let's go meet
Yun Tae-geom's mother.
-Understood.
-Okay.
Monitor the site.
If you find anything on him,
contact me immediately.
This bastard bribed a cop.
I don't know what he used to do.
He's quick and connected.
Perhaps he was a cop.
I see.
Everyone, be safe.
-Woo-jin.
-Here.
-One, two, three.
-Let's do this!
Which camera shows
his direction of travel?
-One moment.
-Sure.
The bottom feed is our best bet.
I'll give you a sedative.
It'll make you feel more comfortable.
No!
I'm doing this on my own!
You may require a liver transplant.
You need to get the shot.
-Or--
-On my own, damn it!
You're putting yourself in danger!
I'll pull through.
Watch me!
-Gang-yong.
-Yeah?
What are you doing?
Woo-jin, do you know how much this costs?
I don't know. About 30,000 won?
Are you kidding?
How much is it?
This costs 250,000 won.
What?
You have to line up at Shinsegae Gangnam
for one of these.
Gang-yong.
Yeah?
Now I know why you brought me here.
Why?
You want me to cozy up
to Yun Tae-geom's mother and work her
so we can get to him in person, right?
I've got this.
Clearly, you're overestimating yourself.
You're talking to the kid.
I'm talking to the mother.
-Understood.
-Good.
Who is it?
-Hello, ma'am.
-Yes?
Could I speak to you for a moment?
Okay.
Two years ago,
he left the country,
saying he'd taken a job in Thailand.
He said he'd run security for a VIP there.
I haven't seen him since.
Not even on the holidays?
No.
Min-a must really miss her dad.
Do you not keep in touch with him?
No.
He must miss his daughter.
I have a daughter just about Min-a's age.
I don't know what he's up to.
I don't want to know.
Good job.
Hey, Min-a.
He's eating all your snacks, huh?
Min-a, can we stop drawing
and do something else?
Let's play with stickers.
I have lots in my room.
Okay, let's go.
Good girl.
So why did her dad leave the military?
Military pay wasn't enough
to cover her mom's hospital bills.
What was her diagnosis?
It was cancer.
Pancreatic cancer.
That must have been so difficult.
Min-a.
Is it okay to waste
all your heart stickers on me?
Yup.
If you put the stickers on your dad,
wouldn't he like that?
I put 100 stickers on him.
When?
Three nights ago.
I see.
Three nights ago, huh?
Then three nights ago,
your dad gave you the scooter, right?
Yes.
How was the ride?
I was too scared to try.
Do you want me to teach you how?
Yes!
Let's go.
Grandma, I'm going
to ride the scooter with him.
I'll make sure
she rides safely and stays careful.
See you later, Grandma.
Be safe.
Of course.
Let's go.
Ma'am.
We already know the truth.
If you help us,
I'll help bring your son home.
I promise.
What do I… have to do?
You just have to call me
when he contacts you.
-Show me the next clip.
-Sure.
Please zoom in.
-Hold it there.
-Sure.
Thank you.
-I'll be right back.
-Sure.
Hello, Woo-jeong.
Yes, I can talk.
I've spotted our Number Four on the CCTV.
You did?
Send me his photo.
-Right away, sir.
-Who?
Number Four.
And, Woo-jeong,
I just met Yun Tae-geom's mother.
His wife had pancreatic cancer.
He took out juice loans for her meds,
but they raided the base
when he missed a payment.
Hence, the discharge.
That's tough.
I know. Poor bastard.
If you have his number, I'll track it.
His mom says
he's always switching numbers.
Should we issue a warrant?
I thought about that, too,
but there could be someone
or even people among us
who took their money.
A warrant will trigger
a total scrub of Yun Tae-geom.
Leave aside Secretary Cho and Yun for now.
That way, the intel will flow our way.
Besides, I want to meet this Yun Tae-geom.
Whatever he is,
the bastard works for his family.
We might be able to flip him.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, send me his photo right away.
Let's see what the bastard looks like.
HONG MIN-BEOM
Hello, Min-beom.
Where are you?
Woo-jin and I are in Daejeon on a case.
Are you okay?
It's rough.
I'm finally awake and calling you.
Thank God.
We were all so worried about you.
Give me a few days.
I'm not out of the woods yet.
Of course, buddy.
I'm hanging up now.
Of course. Get some rest.
There it is.
I feel like a detective right now.
A bit, yes.
-Jun.
-Yeah.
Are you sure she'll be here?
She usually comes to work around now.
I've dropped her off before.
There she is. That's the one!
When you get off the elevator
on the seventh floor,
there's a long hallway.
If you go down that hallway,
on the left,
you'll see a bunch of cards on--
What is this place?
Well, they play blackjack and mahjong,
but that place
is crawling with dangerous people.
There are goons and thugs,
and I've seen people with knives and axes.
Please be careful, Mr. Kim.
Thank you, Mr. Jang.
Good luck.
Whatever it is.
Thanks.
Mr. Moon.
Mr. Min, this is her.
-She's Gi-na.
-Okay.
She works on the seventh floor.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
This is it.
I was here seven years ago.
A serial killer was hiding here.
It was built in the '70s,
so the layout is different.
See the exit stairs?
She'll either come down this way
or take the elevator to the garage.
I need two people to go in
and lure her out.
One person on the exit stairs
and the other on the central stairs.
Gang-yong.
Can I go in the front with Mr. Moon?
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I'll take the exit stairs.
Okay, let's be safe out there.
-Woo-jin.
-Here.
-One, two, three.
-Let's do this!
Let's go.
Got your gloves on?
Damn it.
Yes?
Moon, from Dream On Capital.
I'm here to play.
What's with this fucker?
Who?
Jang Jun sent me.
He said this place is fun.
Time's ticking. Open up.
Is he fucking serious?
Here.
Let's see.
-Hey, go get some more chips.
-Huh?
Man, why do I keep getting garbage hands?
Come on!
Final raise.
-Cops!
-What the hell?
-Fuck, the cops are here?
-Cops!
-Damn it!
-Son of a bitch!
Gun-woo, get her! The pink hair!
You bastard!
Gun-woo!
What?
Fuck!
Get off, bastard!
Stop! Hold it!
I'm not a cop. I'm a small business owner.
So what? You fucker!
-Sir, it's me!
-Stop it! Don't!
-Huh?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
-Are you sure?
Guess I won't die
as long as I stick with you.
She's close. Let's move.
-Okay.
-Man.
Fuck.
-Aren't you coming, Gi-na?
-You go ahead.
Let's go quietly.
Settle down and put the knife away--
Damn it!
Help! Somebody help!
Hello?
-Tae-yeong.
-Yes.
I've got her cell phone. What should I do?
What model is it?
No clue. It's an iPhone,
but I can't tell which model.
iPhones don't need a passcode for photos.
I'm sending you a QR code.
Scan it with her phone.
Got it. Hold on.
GI-NA
MONEY
HOW MUCH
HOW MUCH?
MANJI
GROUP CHAT? WHY NOT DM ME?
IS THE JOB JUICY?
YOUR PRICE PLUS BONUS
LEAVING IT TO YOU
JUST SPIKE A DRINK
USE MY OWN DRUG?
-LET'S TALK IN PERSON.
-WHERE?
I'LL CALL YOU. MEET ME THERE
OKAY
Damn it.
Sir.
What is it?
She put something
in President Hong's drink.
She even met with the person
who ordered the job today.
Where?
Entra Hotel, second-floor bar. At eleven.
Tae-yeong.
Call the hotel
and see if Yun Tae-geom is staying there.
Thank you for calling Entra Hotel.
This is Kang Tae-yeong
with the National Police.
I need the room number
for your guest, Yun Tae-geom.
You must know that noncompliance could
lead to an obstruction of justice charge.
He's a long-term guest in the penthouse.
Thanks for cooperating.
HE'S A LONG-TERM GUEST IN THE PENTHOUSE
We got it.
Gwang-mu.
Please take her somewhere safe.
Will do.
I'll go with him.
-Okay.
-I'll come with you.
Hey.
You said he'd buy it.
Does that look like
a fucking buyer to you?
He's just acting tough.
If we bring Gun-woo, we're good.
Fuck that, you prick.
-What?
-This is the front desk.
Man-bae told me to call
if anything unusual happens.
The police just called the front desk.
SPECIAL OPERATIONS UNIT
Stay inside. We'll take it from here.
Out!
NO CALLER ID
You killed them.
How does it feel?
I told you everyone would be fucked.
I told you one fight was enough,
you son of a bitch!
Why won't you listen?
Your coach's hand is next.
What's your move?
Answer me!
Name your spot.
Good.
Now we're talking.
Wait until I contact you.
Subtitle translation by: Jooyea Lee